[Music]
foreign
is a tool that allows people to save in
a way to address needs in life that once
array payment cannot address and that's
key so we help you build assets over a
long period of time
we also help to be there for you in the
period of time when you need somebody to
hold your hand when you lose a loved one
and you end up you are not in the
position to handle the financial impact
of the loss of a loved one or when a
loved one Falls sick at a time when
you're not financially prepared to
handle the cost of those medical
expenditures
or if once you're working you probably
have to hospitalized and your nature of
your work is such that
you you make money on a daily basis so
if you don't go to work then you lose
your income for the day
life happens every day if you go to the
one bigger and the gay as a market or
any other marketer on their way they
sell Foods people are selling vegetables
people who are working on a day-to-day
basis
if they are hospitalized and they cannot
go to work and for that day they sleep
in a hospital their shops are not open
the stall is not open they cannot sell
Foods they cannot serve vegetable they
lose their money for the day that's why
our Hospital sector product to the
Airtel exists for people who have
purchased this in nights that they spend
in the hospital you pay them up to a
hundred thousand Shillings for the
nights that they spent in the hospital
to compensate them for the money they
lost on their businesses because they
were hospitalized in the hospital if you
have a family member whose health is
your responsibility because you are the
breadwinner so let's say your father
your mother or a significant person
depends on you for their medical
expenses would encourage you to get a
stanbic midi protect plan which is a
health insurance policy which allows you
to put your loved ones on it such that
they can go to the hospital on the
insurance card which is financed by you
they be safe plan allow to save for a
specific period of time for a specific
summer short now what's the summer short
it says that this is the intention you
have in savings if you finish this
period of time we'll give you this
amount of money plus any bonuses for you
that come on board now remember you
might not have saved that exact amount
of money it is a guarantee that we are
giving you by the payment of your first
premium the pool abdicates have abusive
guarantees that the amount of money that
we have assured you let's say 10 million
15 million 20 million 100 million
Shillings by the time you pay your first
premium and your policies issue in next
week Monday or next month something
happens to you and you don't exist again
what happens Prudential will take that
amount of money we promised you and give
it your family members which means that
by the payment of One Premium you have
created an asset our female product
ensures that if anything happens to you
you know your parents your spouse your
significant other
your in-laws people that if they pass
you have a financial contribution to
their burial the moment you get the news
that they've passed away and you're able
to provide information we ask for even
before the funeral is organized
credential is able to pay the money
foreign
[Music]